<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>You Will Change The World Articles</title>
        <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/articles</link>
        <description>Latest Articles from Mentor Around The World</description>
        <item>
            <title>Using a Focus Group for your Real Estate Sales by Melinda L. Goodwin</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/using-a-focus-group-for-your-real-estate-sales</link>
            <description>I work with hard to sell and luxury listings. Let me be the first to tell you that when you are a listing agent for these particular homes you cannot just place a sign on the front yard, put cell phone pictures in the MLS and sit back and wait for other agents to sell your home.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Your First IEP Meeting by Stephanie Wynn</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/your-first-iep-meeting</link>
            <description>Congratulations, you have been invited to attend your child's first Independent Educational Plan (IEP) meeting. Awesome! Now what do I do?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Attention real estate agents! As a real estate agent you are in sales! by Melinda L. Goodwin</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/attention-real-estate-agents-as-a-real-estate-agent-you-are-in-sales</link>
            <description>Attention real estate agents!  As a real estate agent you are in sales!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Forensic Psychiatry by Dr. Greg Brown</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/dr-greg-brown-forensic-psychiatry</link>
            <description>Forensic psychiatry is a subspecialty of the field of general psychiatry. In order to become a board certified forensic psychiatrist, you must first attend medical school, then you are required to complete a residency in general psychiatry, followed by a fellowship in forensic psychiatry.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Keeping Your Eye On The Prize by Greg Jacobson</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/greg-jacobson-keeping-your-eye-on-the-prize</link>
            <description>Lucky for us, we have a choice. As humans, we have the ability to focus our thoughts and imagine any scenario we want.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Entrepreneurial Success Traits: How Do You Stack Up? by Glenn Dietzel</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/glenn-dietzel-entrepreneurial-success-traits-how-do-you-stack-up</link>
            <description>Leaders of the fastest growing companies in America have proven they can fight traditional economic downturns and turn genuine problems into remarkable opportunities.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Finding the Right System/Teacher/Modality by Brent Phillips</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/brent-phillips-finding-the-right-system-teacher-modality</link>
            <description>Our next step is to find a teacher, system, or process to help you develop your intuitive gifts!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Subconscious Mastery of Life by Joe Frazzette</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/joe-frazzette-subconscious-mastery-of-life</link>
            <description>If someone told you that you could create a life of your dreams and imagination just by mastering the subconscious mind, would you believe him? Well I am here to tell you it is absolutely possible!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Better Way To Write Copy For Lead Gen by Paul Talbot</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/paul-talbot-a-better-way-to-write-copy-for-lead-gen</link>
            <description>When your goal is to generate more leads, the process can be as simple as...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Marketing Synergy - Tie It Up with a Perfectly Crafted Bow by Tamra Nashman</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/tamra-nashman-marketing-synergy-tie-it-up-with-a-perfectly-crafted-bow</link>
            <description>Marketing is the elephant in the room, that everyone knows is there, but can’t find. It’s the elusive Goliath that stalks its prey mercilessly, and there seems to be no magic stone to take it down.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A New Way Of Thinking by Greg Jacobson</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/greg-jacobson-a-new-way-of-thinking</link>
            <description>Have you ever been stuck in thinking that didn’t work for you, and you knew it, but stayed with it anyway?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Money Follows Management by Keith J. Cunningham</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/keith-cunningham-money-follows-management</link>
            <description>Robert Kiyosaki, in his book Rich Dad’s Guide to Investing, points out on the opening page, his rich dad’s advice on investing,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Achieving POWER in all your Negotiations by Keith J. Cunningham</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/keith-cunningham-achieving-power-in-all-your-negotiations</link>
            <description>Anytime you are in a negotiation, you are there for one reason and one reason only: To do better than your alternatives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Core Competence by Keith J. Cunningham</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/keith-cunningham-core-competence</link>
            <description>It is so easy to make money when times are good, the wind is at your back and the tide is rising. In fact, for most people, the more they make the smarter they seem to become, venturing into all kinds of investments and side businesses which have nothing to do with what made them successful in the first place.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ignite Your Intuition! Am I Intuitive? And why should I care? by Brent Phillips</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/brent-phillips-ignite-your-intuition-am-i-intuitive</link>
            <description>After you’ve gotten your DNA activated, the next step is to convince yourself that you really canvuse this material to develop and refine your intuitive abilities, no matter your current skill or experience level.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ignite Your Intuition! Intuition and the 12 Layers of the DNA by Brent Phillips</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/brent-phillips-ignite-your-intuition-12-layers-of-the-dna</link>
            <description>Your intuition is arguably the single most important and most powerful tool you can use to achieve health, success, love, happiness, and anything else you can imagine, for both yourself and others.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ignite Your Intuition! What exactly is Intuition? by Brent Phillips</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/brent-phillips-ignite-your-intuition-what-exactly-is-intuition</link>
            <description>Intuition is your 6th sense - or more precisely, it’s really a whole bunch of non-physical senses!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Lights, Camera…Host!!!! by John Burke</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/john-burke-lights-camera-host</link>
            <description>The world of television hosting sure has changed over the last few decades.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Involuntary Commitment by Dr. Greg Brown</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/involuntary-commitment</link>
            <description>During early historical periods, individuals who were regarded as being mentally ill or who acted strangely were often taken care of in the communities where they lived, sometimes performing an important social role.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>In What Direction Are You Moving? by Joe Frazzette</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/in-what-direction-are-you-moving</link>
            <description>What is the first thought you have in the morning? What is the first action you take when you awake? The answers to these two very simple questions are a good indicator of which direction your day will go.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Speaker Training, the Success Secret You DON’T Know, but SHOULD KNOW by Tamra Nashman</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/speaker-training-the-success-secret-you-dont-know-but-should-know</link>
            <description>What’s the one thing that makes a speaker truly unforgettable?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Defining Your Culture by Peter Anthony Wynn</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/defining-your-culture</link>
            <description>In Chapter Nine of my latest Book "Overcoming the Rockstar Mentality" I discuss the importance of defining your culture and the simple elements that cultures all must have in order to thrive.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>You Are What You Believe Subconsciously! by Joe Frazzette</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/you-are-what-you-believe-subconsciously</link>
            <description>Whether you know it consciously or not, we are the sum of what we believe subconsciously.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Competence to Stand Trial by Dr. Greg Brown</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/competence-to-stand-trial</link>
            <description>One of the primary rights that an individual has within the United States is the right to stand trial and to confront one’s accusers in that process.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Market Branding- Dial Down the Excess, Dial Up the Message by Tamra Nashman</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/market-branding-dial-down-the-excess-dial-up-the-message</link>
            <description>Do you know your message pitch? Can you say it in just a few sentences? Knowing the heart of your message, and the way to effectively verbalize it is one of the toughest parts of marketing.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Is good hosting really that hard to do? by John Burke</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/is-good-hosting-really-that-hard-to-do</link>
            <description>The young woman, perfect and coiffed, hears the countdown in her ear and her heart beats a bit faster. The pen she’s holding begins to shine from the sweat of her palms.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Some insight on Mental Health in the Juvenile Justice System by Dr. Susan Feneck</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/some-insight-on-mental-health-in-the-juvenile-justice-system</link>
            <description>Understanding the juvenile justice system can be at times complicated and frustrating especially to the parent or guardian of their child.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Understanding Delinquency and Helpful Hints to Parents by Dr. Susan Feneck</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/understanding-delinquency-and-helpful-hints-to-parents</link>
            <description>What juvenile justice means to you and how to avoid what could potentially be a very difficult experience most often depends on if you are properly informed or not.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Understanding Risks Factors Your Child May Be Displaying That Could Lead To Delinquency by Dr. Susan Feneck</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/understanding-risks-factors-your-child-may-be-displaying-that-could-lead-to-delinquency</link>
            <description>When we think of Juvenile Delinquency, the causes of juvenile delinquency and some of the help available to youth and their families, sometimes it can be so overwhelming that there may seem like there is no hope at all.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Having Regrets? by Donna Kater</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/having-regrets</link>
            <description>From time to time, you may feel some regret about events that happen in your life.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Seeing Ourselves in a Grain of Sand by Donna Kater</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/seeing-ourselves-in-a-grain-of-sand</link>
            <description>Even an everyday grain of sand can be truly extraordinary, if we look closely enough.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>THE EYE OF THE HURRICANE by Donna Kater</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/the-eye-of-the-hurricane</link>
            <description>If you learn just one thing from my teachings, let it be the ability to find your calm center in the midst of the chaos and commotion of life.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 5 Habits of Highly Effective Missional Organizations by Eliakim Thorpe</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/the-5-habits-of-highly-effective-missional-organizations</link>
            <description>If you are reading this article, you are probably asking yourself, "What is a missional organization?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 4 Daily Disciplines of a Successful Entrepreneur by Eliakim Thorpe</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/the-4-daily-disciplines-of-a-successful-entrepreneur</link>
            <description>Throughout the history of the United States; entrepreneurship has been the very engine to our economy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Turning Adversaries Into Allies: How To Resolve Workplace Conflict by Eliakim Thorpe</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/turning-adversaries-into-allies-how-to-resolve-workplace-conflict</link>
            <description>With a rapidly expanding, growing, and challenging global economy; organizations increasingly feel the strain to remain competitive.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ladies Stay Focused by Rev. Kimberly Thorpe L.M.S.W.</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/ladies-stay-focused</link>
            <description>Kimberly encourages ladies to seek God instead of another woman's husband.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Calendar Your Porch Date! by Ann McIndoo</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/calendar-your-porch-date</link>
            <description>I will always remember the day my first box of books arrived.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Preparing to Write by Ann McIndoo</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/preparing-to-write</link>
            <description>The first thing you want to do before you begin writing is to prepare to write – just like anything you do, you prepare.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How Long Does it Take to Write a Book? by Ann McIndoo</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/how-long-does-it-take-to-write-a-book</link>
            <description>Have you ever thought of writing a book? How long have you been thinking about it? How much progress have you made? I meet and talk to people every day who want to write a book. They always ask, how long will it take?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Benefits of Writing a Book: Creating Your #1 Marketing Tool by Ann McIndoo</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/benefits-of-writing-a-book-creating-your-1-marketing-tool</link>
            <description>Why write a book? As a Speaker, Coach, Entrepreneur, or any professional that markets their products and services, having a published book gives you a tremendous advantage over your competition.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CREATING YOUR ONLINE COURSE by Peter Anthony Wynn</title>
            <link>http://www.youwillchangetheworld.com/creating-your-online-course</link>
            <description>Expand your BRAND by Sharing your “Wisdom and Passion”</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>